<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tidyverse on Liz Roten</title>
    <link>/tags/tidyverse/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tidyverse on Liz Roten</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/tidyverse/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing {twohundredfiftythings}</title>
      <link>/posts/introducing-twohundredfiftythings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/introducing-twohundredfiftythings/</guid>
      <description>I decided to get a little wild with my Sunday, so I wrote a tiny R package! I also submitted it to CRAN. Its my first time submitting to CRAN, but I’m feeling hopeful!
{twohundredfiftythings} is a tiny R package that allows the user to access Michael Sorkin’s list of things an architect should know. The list was originally published in “What Goes Up: The Rights and Wrongs to a City”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding the perfect sock pattern with ravelRy</title>
      <link>/posts/finding-the-perfect-sock-pattern-with-ravelry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/finding-the-perfect-sock-pattern-with-ravelry/</guid>
      <description>I am a knitter. Knitting is a calming, fulfilling practice that keep my hands busy and require just enough brain power to keep my mind from wandering too far. Over the past winter, I conquered my fear of making socks, and now I profess that I am a sock knitter. I made socks for Christmas gifts, and churned out four pairs during my evenings, bus commutes, long work meetings, lectures, coffee and tea shop visits (basically everywhere).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota Lakes</title>
      <link>/posts/minnesota-lakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/minnesota-lakes/</guid>
      <description>SourcesDNR Hydrography Dataset
National Wetland Inventory for Minnesota
Lake Bathymetric Outlines, Contours, Vegetation, and DEM
Lake Basin Morphology
Impaired Waterbodies, Minnesota, 2018
Stream Routes - Major River Centerlines
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Housing Density in US Cities</title>
      <link>/posts/housing-density-in-us-cities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/housing-density-in-us-cities/</guid>
      <description>Since I got back from #rstudioconf, I’ve started to warm up to the idea of sharing my code, even if it isn’t perfect. There may be typos, the blog post may be short, but sharing my work is beneficial for the greater #rstats community, and supports open-source data science.
So this belated post is inspired by Cities Start to Question an American Ideal: A House With a Yard on Every Lot, in which the NY Times examines residential zoning patterns in different cities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>